HARY HARSONO

STRATEGIC & DATA ANALYST

HTTPS://HARYHRS.GITHUB.IO



CONTACT

- **** 0813-8328-8525
- ✓ haryharsono96@gmail.com
- Beji Timur, Depok City, West Java Province

SKILLS

- Power BI & Looker Studio
- Google Spreadsheet
- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft Power Point
- Microsoft Excel
 - -Formula Kompleks
 - -Power Pivot
 - -Power Query
 - -Hyperlink Dashboard
- Analysis Skills
- Communication Skills
- Problem Solving Skills
- Logical Thinking Skills
- · Critical Thinking Skills

LANGUAGE

- Indonesia
- English

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Informatics Engineering

Indraprasta PGRI University Year 2019

8

PROFILE

Data Analyst with more than 3 years of experience, especially in reporting analyst and data visualization. Highly motivated to continue developing professional skills. Accustomed to creating interactive dashboards using Excel (Hyperlink), Power BI, and Looker Studio to effectively present data and support the right decision making for the company.



WORK EXPERIENCE

PT. Erajaya Swasembada, Tbk

Strategic & Data Analyst Supervisor

- Review and analyze cost budget vs expenses
- Create ad-Hoc financial forecasting and analysis
- SLA and KPI metrics performance monitoring
- Validate and review performance periodically
- Creating, developing and evaluating dashboards in business performance analysis

Martha Tilaar Group

AUGUST 2023 - APRIL 2024

JULY 2024 - PRESENT

Data Analyst Supervisor

- Pulling master data MTS daily
- Create buffer/safety stock forecasting online
- · Create buffer/safety stock forecasting offline
- · Online and offline store stock monitoring
- · Online and offline warehouse stock monitoring

PT. Global Bintang Timur Ekspress

JANUARY 2022 - JANUARY 2023

Data Analyst Staff

- Pulling master data SLA & JMS daily
- Create operational ritase report
- Create incoming and outgoing report
- Create no SLA report/package stuck
- · Create missed delivery report
- Create troubled package KPI report

PT. Kino Indonesia, Tbk

NOVEMBER 2020 - JUNE 2021

Route Planner Staff

- Pulling master data SFA & IDS daily
- · Create report customer data, routes, salesman
- Create distributor area sales visit report
- Create customer report (Active/Nonactive)
- Create product focus report (Personal Care/Beverages)